<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Juleslovesyou</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Juleslovesyou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gin</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-12-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-12-19/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m trying to write as much as possible while I can. I got my nails done in Korea, and it’s a bit annoying to type because they&amp;rsquo;re too long, but okay.
Afterpay got me promoted to Mint™️ level, and now I don’t even have to pay upfront. The first payment goes through two weeks later, and it’s very much so dangerous. Now my total owing is $1988.55, 5 jobs to go!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Visit Review</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-12-17/</guid>
      <description>Last month, just before the holiday, there was a guy who came in a pharmacist costume. I opened the door, he entered, and he said he would leave because I am different from his expectation. But seriously, is your false fantasy my fault? I explained that I only book one customer a day, so he has to pay for wasting my time. Initially, he refused, but eventually, he paid $100. Hmm… I can only guess; perhaps he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to engage because I was taller than him, and it was intimidating, or maybe I wasn&amp;rsquo;t as attractive as he imagined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Come To Dubai, Habibi</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-12-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-12-12/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wanna meet me in Dubai?&amp;rdquo; L asked.
Jules was in Korea for the first time in 5 years. Pandemic, poverty, the uncomfortable flight seats that make her tailbone hurt for a few days – packing and unpacking that takes forever, Often, she would carry her unpacked luggage from one trip to the next. How about nosy taxi drivers that ask thousands of questions from the airport to home or vice versa?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy One, Get One Free</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-27/</guid>
      <description>I think people these days eat a lot more than they need. What about coffee and alcohol? Think about all those cafes and bars that do shit coffees and musics but still pack of people? People drink and get drunk no matter what the quality is. I feel like they just want to spend some time in somewhere and drink whatever available. It&amp;rsquo;s kinda like being hungry and choosing to eat anything, even poo—absurd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techbros</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-20/</guid>
      <description>What I usually do is that I note random thoughts through the week and organise(write) on Sunday with a sprinkle of GPT&amp;rsquo;s help. (I ask them to fix any grammatical errors) buuuut I had a blast last week so I can&amp;rsquo;t be bothered anymore and didn&amp;rsquo;t think much because I was busy at dinner date etc so there are two types of blogs today one is non-filtered(organic) one, and other I asked chat GPT to rewrite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Discrimination</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-13/</guid>
      <description>Come on, guys! My blog(https://juleslovesyou.github.io) is up and running with no issues at all.
I charge the same amount of money for the rich and poor, old and young, healthy, unfit, ugly, sexy, crooked, autistic, Mensa member, Cenno beneficiary, etc. So, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why many people tell me where they live, how attractive they are, and what they do for a living because have I asked ever
I think it&amp;rsquo;s possibly because men assume that I choose a customer of the day based on their background and hygiene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fifteen Minutes</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-10/</guid>
      <description>I know many girls charge more for short session than longer ones, for instance, $200 for 30 minutes and $300 for an hour, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t, because, to be honest, a 15 minutes session is just as good as a 60 minutes booking. Come, cum and go in 15 minutes feels like I&amp;rsquo;m doing CrossFit or HIIT yet it can feed me 5 times of banana blossom and 10 times of chatime so how can I not like it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Half Forced Post</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-11-08/</guid>
      <description>People tell me to write more but I don&amp;rsquo;t have much things to offer. I in fact write a lot more than I post for example: forequater cutlet, but I know this is not what people expect from me. I used to write about my daddy issues, the relationship struggles and such but who wants to know someone&amp;rsquo;s darkside when everyone has a problem or two day to day. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to give the impression of whinging girlfriend or wife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Bored, Not Lonely</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-10-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-10-31/</guid>
      <description>I don’t know if it&amp;rsquo;s cursed laziness engraved in my bone marrow or if it&amp;rsquo;s a blessing that I&amp;rsquo;m not greedy, but either way, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I worked or wrote something to grab the attention of the bored and horny guys. Last month, I only worked a few days, and HR wanted to talk to me. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t work more than that, dealing with a million light-speed years of commuting and all, especially when I realized that having a bit of fun with three customers equaled my entire week&amp;rsquo;s hard work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PMS</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-10-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-10-06/</guid>
      <description>It is unfortunate that E&amp;amp;B charges me the same amount of money as someone who advertises 7 days a week. It&amp;rsquo;s not the most efficient platform for those who only work occasionally. I&amp;rsquo;d be wasting someone else&amp;rsquo;s time, and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t gain anything by keeping my ad on 24/7, so I don&amp;rsquo;t see the point. Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s only $20 a week, so no hard feelings! I&amp;rsquo;ve been searching for a new platform with innovative ideas for several years now but haven&amp;rsquo;t had any luck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Available</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-09-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-09-29/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my second-week review at MQPK, and I&amp;rsquo;m back a bit earlier than I announced because Thursday was my last working day for this week. I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying the long weekend doing things I love, I always say, &amp;ldquo;Get a hobby (or hobbies); there are much more fun things to do than just having seggs.”
During the first week, I had the audacity to leave my ad on longer than my work hours, which led to being bombarded by &amp;ldquo;Are you available?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s At It Again</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/2023-09-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/2023-09-23/</guid>
      <description>Last November, out of boredom and a desire to buy a Rocket Apartmento espresso machine, I booked a room in Rhodes. The guy who was renting the place at that time is an illegal cat breeder. I don’t know if there are any laws for breeding cats, but anyway, he always had more than 10 cats, and it didn&amp;rsquo;t smell very pleasant. Cats aside, business wasn&amp;rsquo;t that bad, and I wanted to continue working occasionally, but the room was never available again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Size 6, 168 cm, B natural
If you are still struggling to gauge my size(especially when you are an import like me) wearing
Top polo xs
Bottom nudie jean 24w/30l
Lululemon size 0
50 kg on a lucky day
52-3 kg before period
Little over shoulder length straight hair but i curl sometimes
Inked here and there
I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;Asian girl-next-door, which you might walk by without noticing&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
